So far in our dialogue about Luke picking up Mr. and Mrs. Vincent at the airport we've made the basic
到目前为止，在我们关于卢克在机场接文森特夫妇的对话中，我们已经做了基本的
introductions and gone through the we can say the basics asking how the flight was.
介绍并经历了我们可以说询问飞行情况的基础知识。
Now we need to actually recommend or suggest what to do next.
现在我们需要实际推荐或建议下一步该做什么。
Luke needs to say what the choices are.
卢克需要说出选择是什么。
Now I want to mention one point about American culture in particular.
现在我想特别提一点美国文化。
It's usually a good idea to offer options or ask whether what you're suggesting is okay if you say we're
如果您说我们是，提供选项或询问您的建议是否可行通常是个好主意
going to do this and then we're going to do this and then we're going to do this and then we're going
要做这个 然后我们要做这个 然后我们要做这个 然后我们要去
to do this.
去做这个。
Generally speaking Americans will feel like they're trapped and they don't have a choice.
一般来说，美国人会觉得自己被困住了，别无选择。
And that could be an uncomfortable feeling.
这可能是一种不舒服的感觉。
No it's not true in every culture certainly.
不，当然不是在每种文化中都是如此。
But that's generally the idea in America.
但这通常是美国的想法。
So I would recommend if you find yourself in a situation like this with Americans offer some options
因此，如果您发现自己与美国人处于这种情况，我会建议您提供一些选择
give a few choices or make one recommendation and then at the end just ask if that's OK.
给出几个选择或提出一个建议，然后在最后问是否可以。
Which is pretty easy to do.
这很容易做到。
Let's look at how we can do that.
让我们看看我们如何做到这一点。
OK so how about we go to your hotel first.
好的，那我们先去你的酒店怎么样。
This is Luke speaking.
这是卢克说话。
How about we go to your hotel first so that you can unpack OK unpack means take your stuff out of your
我们先去你的酒店怎么样，这样你就可以解包了
bag maybe put your your coat on the hanger and maybe take your shoes out of your bag whatever you need
包也许把你的外套放在衣架上，也许把你的鞋子从包里拿出来，无论你需要什么
to do.
去做。
Unpack your bags and relax for a while.
打开你的行李，放松一下。
OK that's a recommendation.
好的，这是一个建议。
Then we can meet the others and have dinner maybe around 8:00.
然后我们可以在 8:00 左右与其他人见面并共进晚餐。
So we do have a question there at the end maybe around 8:00.
所以我们在最后可能在 8:00 左右有一个问题。
Now if they wanted to they could say well we're really not feeling up to or in the mood for going out
现在，如果他们愿意，他们可以说好，我们真的没有心情或没有心情出去
and having a dinner tonight.
今晚吃晚饭。
So maybe we can just relax at the hotel.
所以也许我们可以在酒店放松一下。
All right.
好的。
That's fine.
没关系。
OK.
或者很遗憾听到有关航班的消息。
Maybe they said it's a terrible was a terrible flight we had turbulence the whole time.
也许他们说这很糟糕，这是一次糟糕的飞行，我们一直都在颠簸。
Well sorry to hear about the flight.
很遗憾听到有关航班的消息。
Now we need to change the topic anyway very good way to do that.
现在我们需要改变主题无论如何都是非常好的方法来做到这一点。
Anyway I hope you enjoy your stay in New York.
无论如何，我希望你在纽约过得愉快。
So I'm trying to shift the discussion shift the conversation to a more optimistic or positive light.
因此，我试图将讨论转移到更乐观或更积极的角度。
OK.
好的。
Trying to push it into more optimistic territory an optimistic space.
试图将其推向更乐观的领域，即乐观的空间。
I hope you enjoy your stay in New York.
我希望你在纽约过得愉快。
I think we can go to the hotel first so that you can unpack your bags and rest for a bit.
我想我们可以先去酒店，这样你就可以打开行李休息一下了。
Does that sound good.
听起来不错。
So this is a straight recommendation.
所以这是一个直接的建议。
This is what I'm saying we should do.
这就是我说的我们应该做的。
Then I want to confirm it.
那我想确认一下。
So you want to avoid saying we will go to your hotel so that you can rest for a bit.
所以你要避免说我们会去你的酒店，这样你就可以休息一下。
How about makes it sound softer and then does that sound good.
怎么样让它听起来更柔和，然后听起来不错。
Allows them to confirm that that's OK and if it's not then they can say so now.
允许他们确认没关系，如果不是，那么他们现在可以这么说。
Sometimes we want to give several choices maybe maybe they want to go to the hotel maybe they want to
有时我们想给几个选择，也许他们想去酒店，也许他们想去
eat right away then I can ask Would you rather this is a great way to offer options.
马上吃饭然后我可以问你愿意这是提供选择的好方法吗？
Would you rather go out and have lunch and then go to the hotel or go directly to the hotel so that
你宁愿出去吃午饭然后去酒店还是直接去酒店
you can rest then they can say what they want to do.
你可以休息，然后他们可以说他们想做什么。
OK.
好的。
Now generally in this situation if I say What do you want to do next.
现在一般在这种情况下，如果我说你下一步想做什么。
It's a little weird because while we're at the airport so we're not going to just stay here.
这有点奇怪，因为当我们在机场时，我们不会只呆在这里。
I guess you could say something like Well where would you like to go.
我猜你可能会说你想去哪里。
But in this situation it's better to offer choices.
但在这种情况下，最好提供选择。
Would you rather go to the hotel now or have lunch first.
你是现在去酒店还是先吃午饭。
OK give some options.
好的，给一些选择。
All right.
好的。
This is how we do that.
我们就是这样做的。
Finally Lydia or David says yep sounds perfect.
最后莉迪亚或大卫说是的，听起来很完美。
What sounds perfect.
听起来很完美。
This plan this thing I'm suggesting sounds perfect.
我建议的这个计划听起来很完美。
I like the plan.
我喜欢这个计划。
Anytime you like a plan you can say sounds perfect.
任何时候你喜欢一个计划，你都可以说听起来很完美。
We learned that with the with the lesson about inviting friends.
我们通过邀请朋友的课程了解到这一点。
We want to change and take a shower as well.
我们也想换衣服洗个澡。
OK as well change means to change your clothes.
OK 以及 change 意味着改变你的衣服。
Then dinner sounds great.
然后晚餐听起来很棒。
Dinner sounds great.
晚餐听起来很棒。
When you make dinner sounds great.
当你做晚餐听起来很棒。
Well what it really means is going to dinner sounds great.
好吧，它真正的意思是去吃饭听起来很棒。
Want to grab a coffee.
想喝杯咖啡。
Coffee sounds great.
咖啡听起来很棒。
Well again yes it is a noun but what you're really saying is it sounds great to me.
好吧，是的，它是一个名词，但你真正想说的是它对我来说听起来很棒。
The idea of going to get a cup of coffee but it's just a simple way to say that.
去喝杯咖啡的想法，但这只是一种简单的表达方式。